I'll be the toast of the town, the girl on the go
奔走在交际圈 大家为我举杯
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我就是那小马 万众瞩目耀眼的光辉
I'll be the one to watch, the girl in the flow
我总站在焦点 无论马群翻飞
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我就是那小马 万众瞩目耀眼的光辉
Becoming as popular as popular can be
我将会变得越来越有名气
Making my mark, making my mark in high society
留下印记 留下印记在上层社会里
I'm the belle of the ball, the star of the show, yeah
我是舞会之王 秀场的星光 耶
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我就是那小马 万众瞩目耀眼的光芒
See how they hang on every word that I speak
瞧他们多么在意我的言语
My approving glance is what they all seek
大家期待着我一句赞许
I'm the crème de la crème, not just another Jane Doe
我是好中最好而不是无名辈
I'm the type of pony every pony should know
我就是万众瞩目耀眼光辉
At home, at the opera, on a fancy yacht
在家 在剧院 在华丽飞艇上
Becoming the talk, the talk of all of Canterlot
在中心城 这里我是大家的向往
I'm the crème de la crème, not just another Jane Doe, yeah
我是好中最好而不是无名辈 耶
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我就是那小马 万众瞩目耀眼的光辉
Because I'm the type of pony
因为我就是那小马
Yes, I'm the type of pony
我就是那种小马
Yes, I'm the type of pony every pony should know
我就是那种万众瞩目的小马